thehansindia.com 2018-11-17

# PRIVACY POLICY - THE HANS INDIA

This privacy policy states how we will respect the privacy of our website users. It says what information we will gather, how we will use it and how we will keep it secure.    

We respect the privacy of the users to this Website. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.    

#### Privacy

Users are invited to submit comments, questions, ideas, reviews or any other information concerning www.thehansindia.com and the website's contents, provided they understand that such comments will be subject to moderation. “Hyderabad Media House Limited” reserves the right to remove or edit such content. All such submissions should not be illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory or infringing on privacy or on intellectual property rights of others.    

#### Privacy

The Website is under no obligation to review any messages; information or content ("Postings") posted on the site by users & assumes no responsibility or liability relating to any such postings. Notwithstanding the above, HMHL may from time to time monitor the postings on the Site & may decline to accept and/or remove any Postings that contain.    

Any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind, including, but not limited to, any material which encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national or international law.    

Advertisements or solicitations of any kind. Messages posted by users impersonating others. Personal information such as messages which state phone numbers, social security numbers, account numbers, addresses, or employer references. Messages by non-spokesperson employees of HMHL & Kapil Group purporting to speak on behalf of HMHL. Messages that offer unauthorized downloads of any copyrighted or private information. Multiple messages placed within individual folders by the same user restating the same point. Chain letters /mails of any kind.    

#### USER CONSENT:

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.    

If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to this privacy policy and be bound by the following privacy policy which is regulated by us to maintain the relationship with you in the relation to this website.    

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use of user information collected on the site to enable the user to make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using this site and its services. It is clarified that any video, image, or other user Content posted at the direction of the user onto this site and the services becomes published content and shall not be considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.    

#### STORAGE OF INFORMATION:

Any information provided by the user to this website shall be stored and held under generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect the user’s personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized personnel are permitted access to the user information and these personnel are required to treat this information as confidential. Despite of these precautions, this website cannot guarantee that any and all unauthorized access to the user’s information will be prevented.    

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? 

We may collect, store and use the personal data i.e., the Information about your visits and Information that you provide to us for the purpose commenting on our published articles. We may collect information about you computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, visit duration and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability.    

#### WE USE COOKIES: 

A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.    

For statistical purposes to track how many individual unique users we have and how often they visit our websites. We collect data listing, which of our pages are most frequently visited and by which types of users and from which countries. Flash cookies may be used to store user preferences for media player functionality and without them some video content may not render correctly.    

We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.    

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookie by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.    

#### USAGE OF INFORMATION:

This website uses IP address information for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. This information is also used to deliver web pages to the user upon request; to tailor the site to the interests of the users and to measure traffic within the this site.    

Any personally identifiable information provided by the user is used to operate, maintain, and provide the user with the features and functionality of the site.    

This website does not use the users email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without the users consent except as part of a program or feature for which the user may exercise an option to not receive such messages. However, we use the users email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.    

#### SECURITY OF INFORMATION:

The website has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of user information, but cannot guarantee such information which will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.    

#### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA:

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.    

#### CHANGE IN CONTROL:

In the event that this website is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, We reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information collected from the users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how will be your personal information may be treated, transferred, or used.    

#### OTHER DISCLOSURES:

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you: 

  1. To the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  2. In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  3. In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);
  4. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. 

#### THIRD PARTY WEBSITES: 

contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.    

#### POLICY AMENDMENTS: 

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.    

This policy was last modified on 20.03.2014(DD.MM.YYY).    

#### CONTACT INFORMATION

The user may contact us with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or comments to webmaster@thehansindia.com .
